Something that people tell me all the time is that, oh my gosh, you like never age.
You're so young.
Because my inner child, healed or not, has always been present.
My inner child has always been in existence.
Part of the reason why I was connected to all of these losers was not only because they mimicked what I needed to heal from, but also because they were inner kids too.
And I was walking up a hill in this park in Korea and it hit me when they say the children will lead us in the Bible.
First of all, stop taking the Bible literally.
Second of all, when they say the children will lead us, it's not the actual children.
Why should the children lead us?
Why should they be leading us?
They should be given the opportunity to be in the safe space.
I was, I was, the only thing I'm allowed to watch during the day is documentaries.
And I was watching this documentary, The Secret of Whales today.
The Secrets of Whales.
And these beluga whales, they, they go into these, this like estuary and they get to have a nursery and they, they're like, why do they travel here?
They travel here because they can have their babies here safely.
The world we should have for the kids, not all right, little niggas, you about to protest.
What?
I'm not saying your kids shouldn't be going to protest, but we should not be waiting on them to save us.
No.
When we say that the children should save us, when we say the children shall lead us,
we are the children who shall lead us because our inner child is the most purest form of our soul.
That's our soul at its purest, most authentic form.
That's our actual soul as nature.
And if you haven't noticed, nature lives in its authentic self and it has managed to maintain and it's only become in threat.
It's only become threatened once we became synthetic.
Once our world became synthetic, I'm getting emotional.
Our bodies became synthetic.
And I looked at the picture on my website and I was like, oh shit, you still have the gloss.
I mean, almost literally because I have on lip gloss.
This picture is synthetic.
You're in a studio, you got the white background.
It has light touch-ups, but touch-ups nonetheless, I don't, I don't want to be the gloss no more.
And when I sit up here and I talk to y'all and I teach y'all, et cetera, I still feel like I'm attached to that.
Because I am, it's like, look at me, all eyes on me, I'm Amanda.
Amanda, and I can't even believe this, but my actual self, Amanda Seals, has become a persona to people.
That's my real self.
And people are attaching the gloss to her.
But I can't blame them because I put her in the mix with the gloss.
And I have no shame and no regrets about that, but once you see it, you got to move.
And I realize, like, no wonder they're looking at you like you're an influencer, nigga.
You over here with titles on your videos and you got promos at the end.
Like, you are.
You are an influencer.
The F people, these coons, when you do it language.
Check yourself.
This feels like the gloss because I'm doing it the same way.
I'm doing this the same way that I would have been doing it in the gloss.
Every week at a particular time when we all come and we all.
And I'm not shading anybody.
Literally, I'm not.
I'm just seeing things for what they are.
And most importantly, I'm seeing myself for what I am.
And in my most authentic self, I am without limitations.
I am without boundaries.
I am weird and raw.
And if you know.